i wouldn't believe it if i i hadn't seen
the magical theme with the coming of
fall
all of the blinking's energy is turned
to harvest to the gathering of the nuts
and berries that will last them through
the long cold storms
[Music]
[Applause]
shine
[Music]
while the blinkins gather their fall
harvest a little girl who lives nearby
thinks of other things
are you ready for our first day of
school belinda
neither am i
i'm sorry i have to spend the whole day
in my backpack but it's the only way you
can go to school and at least we'll be
together
i am sorry but mom says dolls aren't
supposed to go to school
bye
i love you
[Music]
perhaps dolls shouldn't go to school but
they shouldn't be lost in the blinking
wood either
[Music]
[Applause]
hurry up with your harvest blinkings
the first storm of winter may be even
earlier than i thought
how soon i'm not sure yet got to do some
checking but if my calculations are
correct the first snowflake may fall
before the week is out oh no
that's awful we'll never make it you
will have to
get a move on
[Music]
and with the coming of fall sneed a mean
and lazy bear starts thinking of winter
and the long sleep that comes with it
time to get ready for winter
sneed hates winter
nice new house
sleepy
needs something
for what
food
need food for midwife to snack yes
of time though
food
need food
[Music]
this doesn't make any sense
if this is correct
it's going to snow tonight
i don't believe it it hasn't snowed in
the blinking woods this early since uh
it has never snowed in a blinking wood
this early
it's yellow red and golden brown
falling down
happy here
[Music]
maybe we ought to head back guys this
thing is really full oh can't we rest a
minute i'm exhausted
oh you poor thing
well i'm glad someone appreciates all my
effort no no not you i mean her
[Music]
oh take it away i'm going to be sick
it's a lost doll
[Music]
it's heavy
oh
[Music]
it looks kind of
sad it must be very lonely
well i think it's ugly if my hair looked
that bad i'd die
oh no it's the most beautiful doll in
the world
[Music]
someone must miss it very much can we
keep it
we should find out who it belongs to and
give it back oh
gotta move on blinkings this is no time
to be playing with dolls that win a
storm is even closer than i thought it's
going to hit this very night oh no yes
yes
better get that basket of food back to
the winter storehouse fast come on
but mr ben we can't leave this doll
outside all winter what
no i don't suppose we can
i'll tell you what you take the food to
the storehouse and i'll take care of the
dog thank you mr ben
now
what on earth are you doing all alone in
the middle of the wood
[Music]
it's awful cold for this time of year
boy
oh no winter coat
no place to call my own
and i'm hungry too
well hello there mr snead
i need a midwinter snack you get it for
me oh well you see i've been having kind
of a hard time with that myself
[Music]
you don't want to eat me mr snead you
want to eat nuts and berries and honey
and stuff
i happen to know where there's tons of
that stuff
blinkings have got it and with my brains
and your brawn i bet they'd be willing
to share it what do you say
food food mr sneed food fit for a king
partners
well all right
now here's all we gotta do hmm
[Music]
one more nut and i don't think we could
make it
hold it lincoln's
you lost frog
i sent hold at blinkens and i may hold
it
[Music]
you idiot all that work look at this
mess yes stupid green bag of slime watch
it there miss shady you happen to be
standing in front of an ordinary bag of
green slime i am now master of the
blinking wood you and who else wart face
me prince grog and my very dearest and
closest personal friend
emperor sneed
[Music]
spit it out moss patrol
food
[Music]
now boss problems
hmm
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
poor fleshy now don't forget we'll be at
your winter storehouse at sundown
we bring flashy old hillbrain food
don't be late now you're here
and an even worse frog good food
hey right you are boss and there's
plenty more where that came from
so now they've got flashy and they're
gonna show up this afternoon at the
winter storehouse and want all our
winter food supply old sneed he's gonna
be out tonight it's gonna snow bears
don't like the snow they hate the cold
it makes them grumpy talk to him mr ben
tell him to leave us alone
a bear caught out in the winter storm he
gets added headed and confused and he
ends up crashing and bashing into
what will happen to flashy this is awful
when the moon rises tonight the first
snow of winter will fall and that bear
has got to be inside his cave what are
we gonna do mr ben think
of how to trick a bear we don't have
time to think all we need is a moment
any one of us is smarter than any ten
bears or frogs but mr ben
[Music]
wait a minute
what does the blinking queen of winter
look like
there's no such thing
i know that and so do you
but mr sneed the bear doesn't i've got
an idea i think
i'll need your help mr ben to tell all
the other blinkens and i'll need all of
your help too and some fake snow
fake snow
hang on flashy
hang on
[Music]
please let me go
blinking make nice lamp
food
frog promised food
where is frog i'm under here
hey watch out where you sit big fella
time to go get food right you are boss
let's blow this taco stand
[Music]
if there's something important to do
can't save none
[Music]
feel the
is
[Music]
everybody ready
oh no mr ben
we can't do it
it's hopeless
but it's the only hope we've got the
moon
is about to come up the bear and the
frog are on their way to the storehouse
the other blinkens are all ready it's
too late to turn back now come on but
it's not going to work
link it has got to
things happen when they must
make this one happen blink it must
we'll try
[Music]
please
help me
food right the food's in there boss
behind that door
but where's the blankens
hold fast ursus need
oh evening mr ben you love the outfit
but how about you take a hike snead and
i have business here with the blinkins
it's the very reason i'm here
allow me
to introduce
the blinking queen of winter
[Music]
right
come on you guys all together now
miss belinda
the magic queen of winter
sorceress sear
and keeper of the blinking light
[Music]
your majesty
mr ursus need a bear
and
mr grog a frog
would do business with you
it is my pleasure to meet you but what
business is this that calls upon us to
meet like vagabonds on this particular
night
the business we come on is a matter of
food both mr sneed and myself are
silence frog i know why you're here you
would exchange blinking food for
blinking life well i wouldn't put it
quite that way but uh you got the idea
you stupid frog you want food i give you
winter
[Music]
idiot bear
don't you know what this is
sure
it's blinkings
going in a hole
it's blinkings and they are going to
rest going to ground for winter
release that blinking you fool bear
it's going to snow any second
[Music]
release that lincoln or i'll cover you
in snow
oh
[Music]
look around you mr smee
it's snowing
no
it's real snow
hurry up blink
it's too early
i've brought you an early winter as
punishment for your lazy greed
move while you can and take your
thieving frog prince with you before i
decide to bring next winter in july
[Music]
oh i'm sorry mr sneed don't hurt me
how was i to know they had a queen of
winter
you promised me food
my mid-winter snack
i'll get you food all you want i'll get
it myself you'll see a promise
[Music]
flashy
well
queen blinkens
it's not bad for your very first
snowfall
i don't believe i could have done it
better myself but tell me how
did you make it snow
daisies
it's snow daisies dry daisies it was
either that or nuts and berries and even
a bear as dumbest mr sneed wouldn't
believe in snowing nuts
you were right flicker it is the most
beautiful dog in all the world
[Music]
this early winter storm has caught the
tiny blinking community unprepared
[Music]
hmm
i think you blinkings better get home
this storm is gonna get a lot worse
before it gets better
but gee mr ben what should we do with
this doll we found in the woods whoever
lost it will really be sad
don't worry flicker we'll have to figure
out what to do about her another time
maybe he's right
[Music]
bye
oh
i hope this doozy of a storm isn't
blowing a coal my way
[Music]
feeling all the weight of the world
don't throw is all away
we can make you through the storm
together
[Music]
the blinkins are not the only ones
who've been caught off guard by this
early winter storm
[Music]
linda the young girl marnie who lost her
cherished doll in the blinking wood
searches for it in spite of the growing
cold oh
where are you belinda
i miss you so much
linda
oh no
oh you haven't fallen in the river
oh belinda
please don't drown
i'm coming
i love you
winter
snow
time for sleep
set alive for midwinter
kids need mid-winter snack
but mr sneed it's snowing frogs are no
good in the snow
cold frog feet or fried frog legs to
find food for sneeze
oh yeah right right right right boss
anything you say
time force
to sleep
[Music]
where are you
now how am i gonna feed a hungry bear
this guy is bigger than godzilla an
uglier too
at least godzilla was green
what about me
nobody cares about me and my problems i
haven't got one blinking all year
not one
for
go
let me go
[Music]
now what am i going to do
right
[Music]
this storm is getting worse
come on flicker flicker come on
you guys go on home i'll go get flickr
see you later
what's wrong i think i can hear someone
crying but i can't tell where it's
coming from
[Music]
you're right
i think it's coming from the cave do you
think it's safe to go in it it may not
be safe but we have to do something
someone's in trouble
hmm
now this is getting interesting
[Music]
but why is she crying
she is very beautiful maybe she's lost
or something lincoln's aren't supposed
to talk to people can they talk to a
girl
i think so
at least she doesn't look like she'd
hurt us
excuse me oh
i'm sorry i didn't mean to frighten you
but we wondered
are you lost
yes
and and i hurt my ankle too
but
what
who are you
oh we're blinkings blinkings
oh you're wonderful i've never seen
anything so lovely
you're so tiny i am not
well
maybe a little bit tiny
oh you should get home
can you walk no
it hurts
could you go and get me some help
of course oh but blinkens aren't really
supposed to talk to humans blink
i think we should ask mr ben what to do
yes you're right flickr
you wait here with flickr i'll be right
back everything will be all right you'll
see mr ben will know what to do
[Music]
magic
i mean do i get three wishes and stuff
well we're kind of magic
but not that kind
why did you come into the woods
i lost belinda
my doll
and i came out here to find her
you did you mean the dog
[Music]
[Applause]
it
[Music]
mr ben there's a little girl she's in a
cave flicker's there too oh she hurt her
foot and she's lost she's very nice and
we don't know what to do mr ben
one thing at a time please there's a
little girl lost in the blinking wood
well she couldn't have picked a worst
day for it your little girl better get
home quickly or she'll be caught in a
blizzard
but she has a twisted ankle she can't
walk on it oh my mike
oh yeah where is she
i left it with flicker in a cave near
the stream
[Music]
no
a big cave yes
that sneeds cake oh no yes
she wakes up sneed she'll be in more
than a blizzard
you've got to go to her blink but what
can i do something anything but mr ben
sneed's a bear and i'm only a blinking
certainly and i'm an old owl with a goal
but
[Music]
she's a little girl who's in trouble and
hurry blink
[Music]
hurry snow storm will be a full blown
blizzard by nightfall go
okay
[Music]
my dear
yes please i need a bear trap in a hurry
[Music]
well
[Laughter]
you see mr smee
we we we don't we we d we there isn't
that
[Music]
can you make it blink
uh
i hope so
i sincerely hope you can okay
because
i'm afraid i can't
[Music]
stop blink
hello
mr man we found a number of different
plans for that bear trap you need plans
you bleed the trap is built yet oh no we
have this model on back water and some
assembly is required oh but the blankets
need this trap now
immediately even sooner you mean you
want a bear trap no delivered mr ben
we're not superman
where am i
i think i have a way we can work
together
where's fricka
i don't know twink but i don't like it
they should be home by now well i
wouldn't want to be caught out there i'm
gonna go look for them me too
well you're not going out in that
weather alone
okay
i'm coming
oh hi mr ben have you seen blink and
flicker
oh no
too sick to help mr ben spreads the
alarm to all the other blinkings
oh hello mr ben
yes sir
[Music]
and without
hesitation you answer yes
did you bring forward no
no
yes yes i did good
[Music]
eat
wear food right uh
outside
it's outside
it's so big so much food that i had to
leave it outside okay come on let's go
eat uh yeah you guys go ahead i'll uh
catch up okay
all cool
did she bring any food
i hope so
[Music]
snow
but it's huge yeah we can't lift that
that's a problem
[Music]
we must stand together together we can
find the way
and there ain't no mountain we can't
climb
a shout rings out
s-o-s
and without
hesitation you answer yes
like magic
hearts come through the fire
get out of there she can't
wear food
food food uh it's under the snow it
snowed while we were inside waking you
up you wait here we'll get it for you
me too
food
you get it uh we need her help the girl
she's big and we're little and we'll
need all the help we can get to uncover
your huge mountain of food
[Music]
i'm sorry mr sneed but you'll have to
get your own food now come on barney
let's get out of here
no food
no food oh
no yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
you tricks
come on
i can't
[Music]
well well well
hey hey you old bear how you doing huh
oh come on now sneed lighten up i'll get
you some food then i promise
and a frog's promise is as good as
[Music]
even better
blink oh bling clicker
come on blinkings phase two let's get
marty home
[Music]
thank you mr ben
thank you blinkens
i miss you
[Music]
belinda
oh belinda you're back
oh thank you thank you blinkens
[Music]
thank you so much
take care marny we love you
take care
like mr ben
i'm sick and tired as he is
oh
poor mr pin
now you get away from that stove come on
come on you need to take care of this
coal
[Music]
the magical feelings that can flow just
like a dream whenever you help somebody
the moment you do
the goodness will get you it'll bounce
right back to you
making life a better place
laughing at the rain clouds
[Music]
shine